[{
    "question": "`72-:9`",
    "answer": "`8`"
}, {
    "question": "`21-:7`",
    "answer": "`3`"
}, {
    "question": "`72-:8`",
    "answer": "`9`"
}, {
    "question": "`42-:6`",
    "answer": "`7`"
}, {
    "question": "`30-:5`",
    "answer": "`6`"
}, {
    "question": "`30-:6`",
    "answer": "`5`"
}, {
    "question": "`80-:8`",
    "answer": "`10`"
}, {
    "question": "`12-:3`",
    "answer": "`4`"
}, {
    "question": "`24-:8`",
    "answer": "`3`"
}, {
    "question": "`24-:3`",
    "answer": "`8`"
}, {
    "question": "`40-:10`",
    "answer": "`4`"
}, {
    "question": "`90-:9`",
    "answer": "`10`"
}, {
    "question": "`15-:5`",
    "answer": "`3`"
}, {
    "question": "`90-:10`",
    "answer": "`9`"
}, {
    "question": "`100-:10`",
    "answer": "`10`"
}, {
    "question": "`36-:4`",
    "answer": "`9`"
}, {
    "question": "`10-:5`",
    "answer": "`2`"
}, {
    "question": "`24-:4`",
    "answer": "`6`"
}, {
    "question": "`40-:8`",
    "answer": "`5`"
}, {
    "question": "`49-:7`",
    "answer": "`7`"
}]